All
right, good evening everybody. Um,
it's uh
it's it's I I've been smiling ear to ear
for a while now. Uh, you know, after all
the all the high fives and and
everything and kind of settled in, but
um you know, we got Sunny Styles and um
and for I can't tell you how many
reasons why we liked him. Uh but but
it's you can go on and on about him and
uh we're thrilled to have him and so to
pick Sunonny Styles with the seventh
pick um yeah didn't think he was going
to be there. Um thought there was a low
chance there was a chance but um it was
an easy pick when when he when he was
there and we were on on the clock. So um
a little bit about Sunny. Uh I think
he's he's a true commander. He is a true
commander through and through. And that
that's that's what makes one of the
great many things that makes you smile.
You know, you're going to get an
outstanding person in this building, an
outstanding competitor, uh an
outstanding outstanding football
character, everything across the board.
And so, um you know, first and foremost,
a human, great family. I got to meet
them at the at the proday. and um you
know he's he's just kind of everything
you want there as a football player and
a guy in your building in your
bloodstream. So um a little bit about
Sunny as as a player. I mean he's he's
huge. He's he's really like I mean it's
it's just amazing. He's 21 years old.
He's a young guy. Uh he's he's just
scratching the surface, but he's elite
athlete, elite size, elite length. um
and he's just scratching the surface as
a linebacker and he's already really
good and he's only going to get better.
Um that's what gave me a lot of
confidence too is that he's going to get
better and we have the people in this
building with our coaching staff and the
support staff to get him there and then
himself. Uh he's the type of person who
will reach whatever potential he has, he
will reach that potential. Um he's
humble, he's driven, uh he's he's
just kind of checks every box and so it
made it an easy pick. We had a great
visit with him um on the 30 visit. Uh
super impressive, super impressive
football intelligence, super impressive
just presence and just everything about
him screamed commander. And so as a
player sideline to sideline, he can
blitz, he can he can cover, he can play
in the box. He got better as the year
went on. He's only been playing
linebacker for two years and he got
better and better and he played his best
ball at the end of the year. So he's
he's still just still ascending and um
it's fun to watch his progression and
just seeing how much better he got and
how much better he still can get. So,
um, everything across the board,
coaches, scouts, uh, R&D, everybody was,
you got the whole building is behind
him. And so, um, really thrilled about
it. And, um, just, uh, ready to open up
for questions.
>> Kind of think you took everything there.
>> Yeah. Sorry, just rambled.
>> I'm excited.
>> When you saw, you talked about the
improvement made as a linebacker. Where
were were there some moments that coni
that you saw maybe some really big
improvements that kind of convinced you
like he's really taking off. This is a
guy that can keep doing this in the NFL.
>> Yeah, I think it really in every every
kind of um portion of the game, John. I
think um you know, you see him playing
in the box and using his hands and
shedding blocks and and reading blocks
and then getting to the getting to the
ball and and playing like physical like
taking on guards and it got better and
better and then as a blitzer he got
better. Um and I think he's just
scratching the surface there and he's
going to be a great blitzer and um so
all those things that you know come with
changing positions um you saw it kind of
come to life and you saw it in the
playoffs. I mean, he had he played
against Indiana. His game against
Indiana was incredible. Um, and just
made some big-time plays in in the in
the Miami game as well. Indiana was in
the playoffs, but um, you know, you know
everything about them. So,
>> you saw the impact that Warner made in
San Francisco and what kind of can he
make that kind of an impact here and
what what kind of impact could he make
just overall like that?
>> Yeah, I don't want like I probably don't
want to make the mistake of getting into
comparisons. um on that because Fred's
uh you know he's a gold jacket. So you
know if if he can be like Fred then then
we're all going to be really happy. But
um you know Sunny's you know speaking
just about Sunny and his size and his
length and his ability to cover the
whole field. I think those things um for
any NFL linebacker you know that you
covet those things. And so, um, yeah, I
I I I kind of want to stay away from
that knowing how good Fred is and the
person, but they're both, you know,
elite people and, um, they're both guys
that you want in your locker room for
sure,
>> given his versatility kind of how do you
guys envision using him? Yeah, I think
that's one of the cool things because we
have a really talented room, I think,
and and guys that are all very versatile
and so and we have a coaching staff that
is really good about deploying those
guys. And so, I mean, Sunny's a guy who
can play off the ball, he can play on
the ball, um he can he can mug up and
blitz, he there's so many different
things he could do. He'd play Mike, play
Will, play Sam, you know, there all
those different things. He's got the
size to play on the edge. And so, um,
he's really versatile. And so, you we
can kind of mix and match and deploy
those guys and play, you know, as many
linebackers as we can on the field. And
I'm excited to see what the the guys
will do with with Donte and DQ and and
and Ken and those guys like they're
going to they're going to get be able to
get really creative.
>> Um, a two-part question just to squeeze
in another question. Um, did you have an
opportunity to move down and, you know,
would you have taken it if he weren't
still on the board and then Um,
I I'll leave.
>> Yeah.
Yeah. Um, it it was kind of funny. We we
didn't we we did a lot of work on on the
move down. We did we we spent a lot of
time on it. Brandon back there was was
with me looking at all the different
iterations of moving back and and
everything like that. We didn't look to
move up. Um but uh crickets. It was
crickets. So really just looking at my
phone was and nothing. So, um, you know,
we're we're we were so like happy. We
were happy to stay and pick there.
>> Adam, at the, uh, league meetings, I
asked you if you had already at that
point known what guy you want you would
want to get, all things being equal,
when did you kind of was, I guess, when
did you kind of lock in that Styles was
a guy that you did want?
>> Yeah, it it was uh, it is this week and
um, it it was really cool. Well, I just
we got a lot of great input from
everybody in the building. You know,
coaches did a great job. Um, you know,
our R&D and and our scouting department
asked a lot of different guys, all
right, here this group of players who
will likely be there, what's your order
and why? And um, you know, so I was able
to get a ton of different perspectives.
You know, you get Brandon's perspective
um, you know, which is different than a
scout's perspective, which is different
than R&D. So, I really got to see, you
know, all the different sides of the
decision and that really helped
crystallize the decision and then making
it, you know, um just putting together
tapes on all these guys and and you
know, you fall in love with a lot of
them because they're all really really
good players and you know, there's a lot
of really good players that got picked
before us and then some after. But, you
know, Sunny, that that would I felt
really really good about him, uh, really
throughout the process, but certainly,
you know, after the 30 visit and then
this week, um, kind of getting all that
input.
>> And a stated goal for you guys going
into the offseason was get younger, get
faster. Seems like this one guy kind of
epitomizes that, but does that like
combined with everything else you did
with Oay and and Chan, all that is this
really sort of the culmination? I'm sure
you have more to do, but like kind of
the culmination of that. Yeah, he uh he
definitely embodies that and 21 years
old, so he's still really young. Um you
know, graduated high school early. Gosh.
Yeah, that blows my mind, too. But um
and obviously, you know, 44 guy at 6'5,
you know, we're we're really really
fast. He covers a lot of ground. So, um
that's uh it's a big deal in this
league.
>> Good evening, Adam. How are you?
>> I'm good. How are you?
>> You're in a good good mood. Um, so when
you look at the linebacker position
group right now and what were some of
the areas you wanted to make sure you
all got better at and what do you think
you've met that now?
>> Um,
well I think you know looking at this we
we wanted to just get the best player.
We didn't wanna, you know, we didn't
want to draft for need and so we wanted
to get the best player and and you know,
we thought the best player that that was
staring at us in the face was a
linebacker and um so that that room we
feel great about. We felt good about it
going in. Now we feel great about it and
I love the guys in that room already.
They're competitive guys. They're really
athletic. They're they're all guys that
you want to have on your team. So, um
it's just adding more competition and
that's the you really the theme of our
program is competition and those I know
those guys will will all fight and and
create roles for themselves, but um
certainly like happy with the makeup of
that room and and the talent level now.
Yeah.
>> As you look for the rest of the draft, I
guess it's kind of quiet for now until
like, you know, a little bit later
maybe, but um so what's your approach
for the rest of the draft?
>> Yeah, it's a lot of waiting. Um, and
that's that's comes with the territory
when you trade um trade the picks, but
it's a long wait till 71. So, you watch
a lot of guys that you really like go
off the board. And so, um, but yeah, we
just uh getting ready and and and we'll
we'll regroup after this and and see who
comes off the board in the first round.
um and just kind of strategize, you
know, if if this then that in terms of
at pick 71. You know, again, I don't
really see us trading up from 71. So,
we'll just have to sit and wait and um
uh but we're confident we'll get a good
player. It's just a matter of just um
you know, making the best decision for
the team and again just getting the best
player available.
Hey, Adam. I guess it's good that it was
crickets uh that you couldn't hear
anything, but uh when you look at Sunny,
you had a chance to talk to him beyond
just who he is as a player, but that
conversation with him as the person,
what did you see most out of him as who
he is, that person?
um you know he's he is an outstanding
young man and um but you know the words
I would you know just kind of he's he's
mature beyond his years uh I think and
uh he's very curious he wants he wants
to know what the great ones do he wants
to know he wants to be great he's really
humble and uh he's very driven and so
those things you made us all really
confident that he's going to reach his
ceiling
Adam, I'm just wondering what happened
in front of you that made you start to
feel like this was really possible.
Um
the uh
you know, we we the first three were
pretty, you know, we we thought that was
pretty kind of on what we wanted. We
thought that the receiver would have had
like his ceiling was four and probably
his floor was nine. And then with the
Giants um just trying to whatever they
did and I I was I didn't think a corner
would go in front of us but that's also
because you know none of those teams
would have taken them but the trade um
that was probably the when that happened
you know we we were just like okay we we
got this and so so that was that was
kind of the moment. Um but a little bit
nervous, you know, before that, but um
we we felt really good with whoever was
going to come to us and um we just got a
little bonus
>> in particular with with Sunny and to a
lesser extent with Leo, their ability to
kind of take guys up the scene, wheel
routes and coverages and things like
that. What what are some of the things
that now defensively you think, okay,
these avenues are now going to be much
harder for opponents to do to us than
maybe they were able to do to us this
season?
>> Yeah. Yeah. You said both both of those
guys very versatile, really good in
coverage, and then they can both they
can both blitz really well. So, you
know, whether you're they're both up on
the line of scrimmage, one blitzes and
one drops, you don't know who's coming,
you don't know who's not. And they're
they're both really adept at both. So,
that makes that that makes it easier for
us to, you know, we're not so, you know,
one-dimensional. And you got Frankie,
you can do the same thing, too. So, um,
you know, just the versatility of them
and and them be able to line up in
different spots. And they're both, you
know, all of those guys are great
communicators, too. They're all really
smart. So, um, you know, I think it just
kind of makes it it keeps your options
open there.
>> Take three more.
>> As as excited as you seem to be about
him, he seemed just as excited on the
phone that this was his choice. When you
have a guy like that, I don't know if
that was obvious when you met with him
or when he was here visiting that this
was a place he wanted to be, but when
you have something like that, does that
make you want a player even more?
>> Uh, it certainly it certainly helps. I
think um
you know just s getting a chance to sit
down and talk to him and understanding
like you know he's he's really driven
and he's really you know has like the
desire to be great and he wants to be
great for us and and you could and you
could feel that you know a lot of guys
try to sell themselves and and
rightfully so it's a job interview so
that's part of it but um you know his
was genuine his was real he wasn't and
trying and is very comfortable in what
he said. And so, um, it makes you really
confident that, you know, he's he's
going to do everything he can to to be
great and be great for us.
>> Adam, I know you obviously still have
two days left in the draft, but you made
a ton of additions on the defensive side
of the ball through free agency and
adding Sunny, obviously. How would you
kind of assess the improvements that you
made at all three levels on defense so
far?
Um, yeah, I think I think it goes back
to kind of what we wanted to do, just
get younger and faster. And I think
we've done that. Um, but we've we've
added a lot of guys that that we would
call commanders. And so I think that's
that'll never be um that'll be never be
something that we don't do. That'll
always be at the forefront of all of our
decision- making. And so um you know,
getting those guys and they've been in
all week and I wish I'd been more
present with with the team this week. I
was I was not very present this week
hold up in my office a little bit and uh
but uh can't wait to hang out with those
guys next week. But um just the the the
little bit that I did get a chance to go
down to lunch and and walk around the
building and and these guys are all
bought in. You know, the new guys that
we've you know they're bought in.
They're going to dinner together.
They're staying late. They're they want
to they really want to um you know,
these guys really really want to be
great and they really want to learn the
new defense. Um, Donte, you know, I
talked to a bunch of them and Dante has
just blown them away, you know, just the
way, you know, he presents in his
teaching and and so they're really
excited to learn the new defense and so
um, they got new guys that are they're
hungry. They're hungry to prove
themselves and hungry to to to learn and
so um, it's it's been really exciting to
see.
>> Hey, bud. Um, you mentioned Sunny as the
person more than more than just the
player and talk about getting to know
his family. obviously comes from a
football family. His brother's a player.
His mother is fully ingrained in the
football lifestyle. How how key is that
for a young guy to be able to have
success not just in a big-time college
program, but also taking the step to the
NFL?
>> Yeah, you always, you know, I you want
to bet on the the stock, you know, and
bet on somebody who's been around it and
somebody who who knows what it's what
it's like. And so, um, that's that's
always a bonus, not a requisite, but
it's always it's always helps. and
understanding even if you're not, you
know, even when you're little, you just
kind of understand like what it takes
and and you can tell that his parents
have instilled that in him just that his
how mature and responsible and um you
know driven he is. He's he's been raised
really well, but at the same time like
he's he's just like guy you want your
daughter to marry. And so, um, you know,
all of those things. And so, yeah, he's
he's been raised really well and and
certainly been around football. So, um,
that that is a big bonus for sure.
>> Appreciate it.
>> All right, guys.
>> Huh?
>> I did.
>> You guys guess what he wanted, but uh,
no, he he said he just said good luck
and and you know, everything. He was
super supportive. It was good good to
see him and and um you know he's he's uh
he's uh he's had a good weekend. It's
been really really fun to see him and
and uh everybody's been really
impressed. So um but yeah, he he uh he
honestly he just showed his support.
Yeah.